<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Deploy CloudFront Extensions on CloudFront Extensions</title><link>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/workshop/deploy/</link><description>Recent content in Deploy CloudFront Extensions on CloudFront Extensions</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/workshop/deploy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deploy CloudFront Extensions Console</title><link>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/workshop/deploy/deploy-console/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/workshop/deploy/deploy-console/readme/</guid><description>Time to deploy: Approximately 20 minutes
Deployment steps Sign in to the AWS Management Console and select the button to launch the CloudFormation template. You can also download the template as a starting point for your own implementation.
We launch this template in US East (N. Virginia) Region, please check the region on the right-upper corner and make sure it is correct.
Choose Next.</description></item><item><title>Setup monitoring</title><link>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/workshop/deploy/setup-monitoring/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/workshop/deploy/setup-monitoring/readme/</guid><description>In this section, we will enable CloudFront standard log and monitor CloudFront metrics on CloudFront Extensions console.
After deployment, you will see two CloudFormation stacks.
Setup monitoring by following steps:
Go to CloudFormation console
Switch View nested on. Choose the Outputs tab of the nested stack (the stack whose name contains NonRealtimeNestedStack).
You will find the S3 bucket in S3buckettostoreCloudFrontlogs. Copy the S3 bucket name.</description></item><item><title>Setup SSL notification</title><link>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/workshop/deploy/setup-ssl/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/workshop/deploy/setup-ssl/readme/</guid><description>You can use CloudFront Extensions to automatically create or import SSL Certificates and associate them to new CloudFront distributions. Before that, you need to setup SSL notification.
After deployment, you will receive an email with the title AWS Notification - Subscription Confirmation
Setup SSL notification by following steps:
Click Confirm subscription link in the email. It will go to a web page which indicates the subscription is confirmed.</description></item></channel></rss>