<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Prerequisite on CloudFront+</title><link>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/prerequisite/</link><description>Recent content in Prerequisite on CloudFront+</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/prerequisite/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AWS CloudShell</title><link>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/prerequisite/aws-cloudshell/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/prerequisite/aws-cloudshell/readme/</guid><description>AWS CloudShell is a browser-based shell that makes it easy to securely manage, explore, and interact with your AWS resources. CloudShell is pre-authenticated with your console credentials. Common development and operations tools are pre-installed, so no local installation or configuration is required. With CloudShell, you can quickly run scripts with the AWS Command Line Interface (AWS CLI), experiment with AWS service APIs using the AWS SDKs, or use a range of other tools to be productive.</description></item><item><title>AWS CDK</title><link>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/prerequisite/aws-cdk/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/prerequisite/aws-cdk/readme/</guid><description>The AWS Cloud Development Kit (AWS CDK) is an open source software development framework to define your cloud application resources using familiar programming languages.
AWS CDK is not pre-installed in AWS CloudShell currently, so you will need to install it
Install the AWS CDK Toolkit globally using the following Node Package Manager command.
npm install -g aws-cdk You will need to add sudo in front of the command If you see below error</description></item><item><title>Configuring the AWS CLI</title><link>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/prerequisite/aws-cli-configure/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/prerequisite/aws-cli-configure/readme/</guid><description>This section explains how to configure the settings that the AWS Command Line Interface (AWS CLI) uses to interact with AWS. These include your security credentials, the default output format, and the default AWS Region.
You can configure AWS CLI by enter following command
aws configure The following example shows sample values. Replace them with your own values as described in the following sections.
$ aws configure AWS Access Key ID [None]: AKIAIOSFODNN7EXAMPLE AWS Secret Access Key [None]: wJalrXUtnFEMI/K7MDENG/bPxRfiCYEXAMPLEKEY Default region name [None]: us-east-1 Default output format [None]: json</description></item></channel></rss>