<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Prerequisite on CloudFront Extensions</title><link>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/workshop/prerequisite/</link><description>Recent content in Prerequisite on CloudFront Extensions</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/workshop/prerequisite/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deploy Sample Website</title><link>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/workshop/prerequisite/sample-website/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/workshop/prerequisite/sample-website/readme/</guid><description>Time to deploy: Approximately 15 minutes
Launch Stack Sign in to the AWS Management Console and select the button to launch the CloudFormation template. You can also download the template as a starting point for your own implementation.
!!! Note &amp;ldquo;Note&amp;rdquo; This template is created for us-east-1 region (N. Virginia) and will not work in other regions.
The template can only be launched in US East (N.</description></item><item><title>Check Stack Output</title><link>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/workshop/prerequisite/sample-check/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/workshop/prerequisite/sample-check/readme/</guid><description>Once the CloudFormation deployment is finished, please review the output tab.
Navigate to CloudFormation console.
Open CFExtSampleWorkshop stack (or the one you named during the CloudFormation installation).
Select the Outputs tab of the menu.
You will see 5 outputs such as below. Keep this page open, or capture them separately. Record the DistributionID and DemoDefaultUrl since we will use them in further section.</description></item><item><title>Specify a query result location for Athena</title><link>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/workshop/prerequisite/setup-athena/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/workshop/prerequisite/setup-athena/readme/</guid><description>!!! Note &amp;ldquo;Note&amp;rdquo;
The solution uses Athena to query CloudFront logs, **if this is the first time you use Athena in the region**, you are required to specify the location for query results in Athena, or else you can skip this section. Before you can run a query, a query result bucket location in Amazon S3 must be specified.
To specify a client-side setting query result location using the Athena console</description></item></channel></rss>