<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Prerequisite on CloudFront Extensions</title><link>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/workshop/prerequisite/</link><description>Recent content in Prerequisite on CloudFront Extensions</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/workshop/prerequisite/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AWS CloudShell</title><link>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/workshop/prerequisite/aws-cloudshell/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/workshop/prerequisite/aws-cloudshell/readme/</guid><description>AWS CloudShell is a browser-based shell that makes it easy to securely manage, explore, and interact with your AWS resources. CloudShell is pre-authenticated with your console credentials. Common development and operations tools are pre-installed, so no local installation or configuration is required. With CloudShell, you can quickly run scripts with the AWS Command Line Interface (AWS CLI), experiment with AWS service APIs using the AWS SDKs, or use a range of other tools to be productive.</description></item><item><title>AWS CDK</title><link>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/workshop/prerequisite/aws-cdk/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/workshop/prerequisite/aws-cdk/readme/</guid><description>The AWS Cloud Development Kit (AWS CDK) is an open source software development framework to define your cloud application resources using familiar programming languages.
AWS CDK is not pre-installed in AWS CloudShell currently, so you will need to install it
Install the AWS CDK Toolkit globally using the following Node Package Manager command.
sudo npm install -g aws-cdk Run the following command to verify correct installation and print the version number of the AWS CDK.</description></item><item><title>Configure your credentials</title><link>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/workshop/prerequisite/aws-config/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/workshop/prerequisite/aws-config/readme/</guid><description>To configure your credentials, run below command
aws configure Type your credentials and type us-east-1 in terms of region name
AWS Access Key ID [None]: &amp;lt;type your access key id&amp;gt; AWS Secret Access Key [None]: &amp;lt;type your secret access key&amp;gt; Default region name [None]: us-east-1 Default output format [None]: If you forget the credentials, you need to create a new one in IAM console</description></item></channel></rss>