<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>WAF &amp; Shield Best Practice on CloudFront Extensions</title><link>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/security-practice/</link><description>Recent content in WAF &amp; Shield Best Practice on CloudFront Extensions</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/security-practice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deploy OWASP Juice Shop</title><link>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/security-practice/juice-shop/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/security-practice/juice-shop/readme/</guid><description>In this section you will deploy the OWASP Juice Shop by CloudFormation stack, first please deploy the Juice Shop Web Application in US East (N. Virginia) (us-east-1) region.
This CloudFormation stack will take approximately 5 minutes to complete. Step by step instructions:
Provide your stack with a unique name. Note: Be careful not to exceed the 64-character stack name limit Click the “Next” button at the bottom of the remaining pages, using the default values.</description></item><item><title>Deploy WAF &amp; Shield Automations</title><link>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/security-practice/deploy/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/security-practice/deploy/readme/</guid><description>Deploy WAF &amp;amp; Shield Automations Please follow this previous step to Upload CloudFront Extensions code into CloudShell if have not unzipped the CloudFront Extensions repository in the CloudShell.
After unzipping the aws-cloudfront-extensions archive, you can deploy the WAF &amp;amp; Shield Automations in the CloudShell by the next commands:
Create a symbolic link to PIP from PIP3
sudo ln -s /usr/bin/pip3 /usr/bin/pip Change the current directory to &amp;lsquo;aws-cloudfront-waf/deployment&amp;rsquo;</description></item><item><title>Web ACLs and Managed Rules</title><link>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/security-practice/rule-testing/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/security-practice/rule-testing/readme/</guid><description>In this step of the workshop, you will see how the AWS WAF protects against common attacks, such as SQL injection or Command Line attacks.
Introduction Web ACLs A web ACL (Web Access Control List) is the core resource in an AWS WAF deployment. It contains rules that are evaluated for each request that it receives. A web ACL is associated to your web application via either an Amazon CloudFront distribution, AWS API Gateway API or an AWS Application Load Balancer.</description></item><item><title>Prevent DDoS attacks</title><link>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/security-practice/flood-testing/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://awslabs.github.io/aws-cloudfront-extensions/security-practice/flood-testing/readme/</guid><description>In this step of the workshop, we will demonstrate the functionality provided by the WAF &amp;amp; Shield Automations Solution to detect this type of attack and block the responsible IP address in AWS WAF.
Introduction HTTP flood rule protects against attacks that consist of a large number of requests from a particular IP address, such as a web-layer DDoS attack or a brute-force login attempt. With this rule, you can set a threshold that defines the maximum number of incoming requests allowed from a single IP address within five minutes.</description></item></channel></rss>